Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VII: Photographic material, 1960-2010
  - Subseries 3: People, 1960-1998
    - General Sugita, Japan, undated (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Tom Sullivan, undated (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Tom Sullivan, Debbie Boone, Cast E, undated (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Tell Taylor, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Jerry Von Teuber, undated (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - Professor Enrique Tierno Galvar, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Charles Thomas, undated (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Charles Thomas; Langhorne, Washburne; Winters, Jonathan, undated (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - Reed Thompson, Cast B, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - J. Thompson, undated (Box 56, Folder 48)
    - Senator Strom Thurmon, undated (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - John Tower, undated (Box 56, Folder 50)
    - Virginia Trevitt, undated (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - Jim Troutner, undated (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - Pierre Trudo, undated (Box 56, Folder 53)
    - Paul Tsosie, undated (Box 56, Folder 54)
    - Jean Luc Tursern, undated (Box 56, Folder 55)
    - Senator Morris Udall, Arizona, 1976, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 56)
    - Unidentified Individuals, undated (Box 56, Folder 57)
    - Cecillo Valverde, President of National Senate Spain, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 58)
    - Janet Vazquez, undated (Box 56, Folder 59)
    - Della Vida, undated (Box 56, Folder 60)
    - Rodolfo Martin Villa, Minister of Territorial Admin, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 61)
    - Mr. Vince, Mercedes Benz, undated (Box 56, Folder 62)
    - Governor Vinnear, undated (Box 56, Folder 63)
    - VIPs, undated (Box 56, Folder 64)
    - Pete Voevodsky, undated (Box 56, Folder 65)
    - Rusty Wailes, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 66)
    - Dewitt Wallace, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 67)
    - Governor Wallace, Alabama, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 68)
    - Langhorne Washburn, undated (Box 56, Folder 69)
    - Seiki Watanabe, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 70)
    - Cyndi Watson, undated (Box 56, Folder 71)
    - Don Weiss, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 72)
    - Erwin Wenzl, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 73)
    - Jean Whittouck, Belgium Symphony, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 74)
    - Ruth J. Wickemeyer, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 75)
    - Williams F. Wilkes, 1977, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 76)
    - Wilkens, NAACP, undated (Box 56, Folder 77)
    - Governor Jack Williams, Arizona, undated (Box 56, Folder 78)
    - Pam Williams, undated (Box 56, Folder 79)
    - Mandell de Windt, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 80)
    - Jonathan Winters, undated (Box 56, Folder 81)
    - Bill Wishward, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 82)
    - Bill Woestendiek, Arizona Daily Star, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 83)
    - Steve and Terry Woods, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 84)
    - Benjamin Woodson, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 85)
    - Guy Woolford, undated (Box 56, Folder 86)
    - Buki Wright, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 87)
    - Bruce Yansey, undated (Box 56, Folder 88)
    - Pepe Zarzaneclas, undated (Box 56, Folder 89)
  - Subseries 4: Performances and Events, 1965-1999
    This series contains photographs, negatives and slides related to various Up with People performances and events including alumni events, international tours and community service. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - 7305-1-8, undated (Box 56, Folder 90)
    - Acoustics, undated (Box 56, Folder 91)
    - Acoustics, Nursing homes and hospitals (1 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box 56, Folder 92)
    - Acoustics, Nursing homes and hospitals (2 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box 56, Folder 93)
    - Africa, Smithfields (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 94)
    - Africa, Smithfields (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 95)
    - AHL, undated (Box 56, Folder 96)
    - Alaska, Cast E, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - ALFA, Mexico, December, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Alumni activities, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Alumni activities, signing autographs, 1969-1971 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Alumni activities, Super Bowl XIV, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1976-1977 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Reunion (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Reunion (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Reunion (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Reunion (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Reunion (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Reunion (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Reunion (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Reunion, undated (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Reunion, Loews, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Reunion, Mexican Reunion, 1979-1995 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Reunion, “Sing Out”, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - American Bankers Association, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - American Newspapers Publishers, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Annapolis, Baltimore Colts, NY Jets, cast A, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Aquippa, Pennsylvania, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - ARCO Jesse Owens Games, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - ARCO Jesse Owens Games, Los Angeles, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Argentina, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Argentina, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Arizona Broadcast Association, August, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Arizona, Phoenix Coliseum, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Arizona State Capitol, Phoenix, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Statehood Day, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Arizona, Tucson, Pueblo High School, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Arizona, Tucson, Udall Dinner, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Arneson River Theatre, Texas, San Antonio, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Ashby’s and Smithfield, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Asian Society Reception, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Assembly, Colorado, Alamosa, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Assembly, Elementary School, 1973-1981 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Assembly, Hospital, 1976-1978 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Assembly, Hospital, undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Assembly, Mall Show, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Assembly, Michigan, Detroit, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Assembly, Miscellaneous, 1972-1981 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Assembly, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Assembly, Nursing Home, undated (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Assembly, Prison, 1972-1977 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Assembly, School for the Handicapped, 1973-1976 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Associated Press Convention, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Associated Press Convention, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Audiences, 1968-1976 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Audiences, 1976-1982 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Audience, Cast E, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Audience, Children (1 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Audience, Children (2 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Audience Shots, General, 1978-1981 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Audience, Veterans Administration Medical Center, Texas, Amarillo, March, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Australia, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Australia, Brisbane, Cast E, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Australia, Cast E, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Australia, Smithfields, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Australia, Sydney, Cast E (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Australia, Sydney, Cast E (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Australia, Toowoomba, Cast E, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Bangor Symphony, Maine, Cast E, 1984 July (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Beat of the Future, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Belgium, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Belgium, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Belgium, 1971-1972 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Belgium, 1973-1975 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Belgium, Cast E, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Belgium, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Belgium, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Belgium, Spring, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Belgium, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Belgium (1 of 2), undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Belgium (2 of 2), undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Belgium National Symphony, November, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Bermuda, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Bermuda, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Bermuda, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Bermuda (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Bermuda (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Bermuda, undated (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Biltmore House, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Black and White, Cast E, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Black Tie Gala (1 of 3), 1993 July 22 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Black Tie Gala (2 of 3), 1993 July 22 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Black Tie Gala (3 of 3), 1993 July 22 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Black Tie Gala- Kids Program (1 of 2), 1993 July 22 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Black Tie Gala- Kids Program (2 of 2), 1993 July 22 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Black Tie Gala- Public Dedication (1 of 2), 1993 July 23 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Black Tie Gala- Public Dedication (2 of 2), 1993 July 23 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Blossom Center, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Board meeting, 1987, 1992 June (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Board meeting, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Bob Hope Special, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Boise River Festival, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Boston Market, AFNB, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Boston Pops, (1 of 2), 1982 September (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Boston Pops, (2 of 2), 1982 September (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Boys Club of America, 1982 August (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Boys Scouts Kamboree, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Broadcasters Convention, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Brotherhood of Man Dinner, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Bunker Hill, undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - California, Arcadia, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - California, Oakland, Cast E, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - California, San Francisco, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Calgary Stampede, undated (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Campaign Kick-off, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Canada, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Canada, 1976-1978 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Canada, 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Canada, British Columbia, Fall, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Canada, Cast E, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Canada Prime Minister, Brian Mulroney October, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Career development, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Carnegie Hall, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Carnegie Hall, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Cast community event photos, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Cast event, undated (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Cast travel photos, undated (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Catalina Island, Cast B, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Cheeseborough-Ponds, Cast B, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - China (1 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - China (2 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - China (3 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - China (4 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - China (5 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - China (6 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - China (7 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - China (8 of 8), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - China (1 of 4), 1985 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - China (2 of 4), 1985 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - China (3 of 4), 1985 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - China (4 of 4), 1985 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - China, Spring, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Gym, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Chinese Gymnastic Delegation, Cast B, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Cleveland Kick-off, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - College Gym Show, undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Colorado Association of Black Professional Engineers and Scientists Summer, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Colorado, Denver, Miscellaneous Shows, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Colorado Leaders Business Luncheon, 1996 February 28 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Colorado, Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Colorado Rockies, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Colombia, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Colwell-Allen Tribute (1 of 2), 1975 July 25 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Colwell-Allen Tribute (2 of 2), 1975 July 25 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Colwell Brothers, Smithfields, John Roots, undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Community Involvement, 1977-1981 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Community Involvement, 1981-1984 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Community Involvement, undated (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Community Involvement, Acoustics, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Community Involvement, Acoustics, undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Community Involvement, Cast C, Colorado, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Community Involvement, Cast D, Battle Creek, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Community Involvement, Day in Tucson, 1981 August (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Community Involvement, Ireland, 1994 March (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Community Involvement, Indian Reservation, 1971-1981 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Community Involvement, Michigan, Detroit, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Community Involvement, Navajo Family, undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Community Involvement, Ohio, Cleveland, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Community Involvement, Show Assembly, undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Community Involvement, West Portal, Elementary School, undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Community Service (1 of 2), 1980-1995 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Community Service (2 of 2), 1980-1995 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Community Service, 1998 May (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Community Service (1 of 2), undated (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Community Service (2 of 2), undated (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Conga Line, 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Congo, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Contact sheets, 1973 March-April (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Contact sheets, 1976 June-July (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Contact sheets, 1976 August (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Contact sheets, 1976 September (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Contact sheets, 1976 October (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Contact sheets, 1976 November (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Contact sheets, 1976 December (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Contact sheets, 1977 January (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Contact sheets, 1977 February (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Contact sheets, (1 of 2), 1977 March (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Contact sheets, (2 of 2), 1977 March (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Contact sheets, (1 of 2), 1977 April (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Contact sheets, (2 of 2), 1977 April (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Contact sheets, 1977 May (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Contact sheets, 1977 June (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Contact sheets, (1 of 2), 1977 July (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Contact sheets, (2 of 2), 1977 July (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Contact sheets, (1 of 2), 1977 August (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Contact sheets, (2 of 2), 1977 August (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Contact sheets, 1977 September-October (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Contact sheets, 1977 November- December (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Contact sheets, 1978 January (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Contact sheets, 1978 February- April (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Contact sheets, 1978 May (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Contact sheets, 1978 June- July (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Contact sheets, 1978 August (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Contact sheets, 1978 September (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Contact sheets, 1978 October- December (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Contact sheets, 1979 January- February (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Contact sheets, 1979 May-July (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Contact sheets, 1979 August-September (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Contact sheets, 1979 September-October (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Contact sheets, J. Blanton Belk, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Contact sheets, Casts, Staging and show shots, 1979-1981 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Contact sheets, Unidentified, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Contact sheets, Unidentified (1 of 2), undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Contact sheets, Unidentified (2 of 2), undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Copper Days, Tucson, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Corporate Tour, 3M, Minnesota, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Corporate Tour, Buick, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Corporate Tours, Chevrolet, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Corporate Tours, Days Inn Tour, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Corporate Events, First National Bank of Boston, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Corporate Tours, First National Bank of Boston (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Corporate Tours, First National Bank of Boston (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Corporate Tours, First National Bank of Boston (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Corporate Tours, General Electric, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Corporate Tours, General Electric, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Corporate Tours, General Electric, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Corporate Tours, General Electric Canadian, Cast B, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Corporate Tours, General Motors, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Corporate Tours, General Motors, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Corporate Tours, Honeywell, Cast B, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Corporate Tours, Kodak Tours (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Corporate Tours, Kodak Tours (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Corporate Tours, McDonalds Tour, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Corporate Tours, Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Tours, Mountain Bell, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Tours, Panasonic, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Corporate Tours, Pepsico, Don Kendall CEO, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Corporate Tour, Ritz Carlton Chicago, 1981 November (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Corporate Tour, Scott Paper Co., 1979 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Tours, Scott Paper Co., 1980 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Corporate Tours, Sun Company, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Corporate Tour, Tenneco, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Costa Rica, Spring, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Cotton Bowl, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Countries, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Dallas Symphony, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - David Whiting, Julio Zamora, Cast A, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Day in Colorado, Denver, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Decatur Place, 1995 February 9 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Decatur Place/Wrap up Summer, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Denver Broncos, 1993 November 21 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Denver Children’s Museum- Dog Shelter, 1995 February (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Denver Diabetes Association, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Denver Symphony, 1979 September (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Denver Symphony, 1981 September 11 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Denver Symphony, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Department of Social Services Summer, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - DeWitt Wallace Lunch, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Dodgers Stadium, 1981 April (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Dorothy Chandler Benefit, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - D.U.G., Summer, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Economic Club, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Education, 1976-1978 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Education, undated (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Education, career days, undated (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Education, C.I.D. classroom visit, undated (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Education, Miscellaneous, 1970-1979 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Eli Lilly 4-H, Chicago, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Elton Cary Lunch, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - England, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - England, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Epcot Center, Orlando Florida, Cast D, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Estonia, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Europe, 1977-1979 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - European Convention, undated (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - Event slides for checkout, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - Expo, 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - Expo, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Expo, Cast B, 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Expo, Japan, Osaka, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Expo, Montreal, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Face to Face, Cast E, 1989-1991 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Face to Face, Promo Dupes, Cast E (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Face to Face, Promo Dupes, Cast E (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Family of Man, New York, Hilton, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Fashion Shots, Cast C, 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Fashion Show, Cast A, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Festival in the Sun, Tucson, undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - 50’s Cast, Cast E, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Filene Center, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Finland, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Firestone’s Home, Cast C, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Florida Race Track, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Food Bank of the Rockies, Summer, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Fort Lauderdale Symphony, Cast C, 1979 January (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Fort Slocum, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Fort Worth, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Fountainhead, Cast C, undated (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - France, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Georgia, Atlanta, Cast A, High school, undated (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Germany, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Germany, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Germany, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Germany, 1973, 1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Germany, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Germany, Munich, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Germany, Rostock, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Gissler Hyannis Symphony, Cast A, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Gospel Stage and Studio, Cast E, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Habitat for Humanity, 1995 February (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Habitat for Humanity, Summer, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Half-time Baltimore, Cast B, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Half-time Giants Football, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Half-time Seattle Seahawks, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Harborfest, Norfolk, Virginia, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Hollywood Bowl, Los Angeles, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Honolulu City Hall, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Host Families, undated (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Hyatt Regency, Cast A, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - ICG, undated (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Idaho, Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - IDS Center, Minneapolis, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Illinois, Chicago, Cast C, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Illinois, Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Inaugural Parade, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Indian Reservation (Tohono O'odham Reservation), Sells, Arizona, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Indiana, Indianapolis, 1976-1984 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Indiana University Track Meet, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Indianapolis 500, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Indianapolis 500, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Indianapolis Symphony, Cast C, 1980 June 18 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Instruments, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Intercultural Education, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Interlocken site, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - IBM, Cast C, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - IBM Dedication, 1980 October (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - International Clowns, Cast E, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - International Costumes, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - International Costumes, Cast E, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - International Fair, Nevada, Cast E, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - International Small Group Shot, New York, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Ireland, 1974-1978 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Italy, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Italy, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Italy, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Italy (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Italy (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Italy, Cast A, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Italy, Montico, undated (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - IU, undated (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Jackson Hole, Filene Center, Cast B, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 29)